

in linkedin.com/in/sampconrad

- github.com/sampconrad
- 🔀 sampconrad@gmail.com
- +55 86 981-736-610

CONRADO SAMPAIO

Full-Stack Developer

ABOUT ME

After being unhappy with my career post college, I started a web dev course on a whim and fell in love with it. Through this journey I acquired a solid understanding of Front and Back-end development tools, but it is the former I enjoy the most.

With a strong focus on clean responsive design and fluid user experiences, I'm building full-stack projects and sharing their code over at sampconrad.com.

_

_{JS} JavaScript

5 HTML

SKILLS

₹ CSS

SASS

B Bootstrap

Tailwind

F Figma



💪 Redux

Node.JS

EX Express.JS

♠ MongoDB

PostgreSQL

♦ Git

EDUCATION

System Analysis & Development

Uninassau 2021 - 2022

Bachelor of Laws

CEUT | Estácio 2011 - 2016

EXPERIENCE

IT Consultant

Self Employed 2018 - 2022 Freelance work providing IT solutions and remote technical support to clients.

Lead IT Specialist

Gracom 2017 - 2017

On-site tech support in charge of the IT infrastructure of an Adobe-certified school of graphical design.

Want to know more?



Scan the QR code to view my portfolio at:

www.sampconrad.com